And I'm teaching the steps
along the way.
The plan is a 15-year plan. Wifi
Yamaguchi,
your best seventh, 15, sometimes, as they say,
50.
[Music]
And we've already finished eight years,
and then a lot of people didn't come at the
beginning,
so I'm going over
the previous years. Every day I do, we're going
to do previous teachings.
[Music]
The role they've been given to help them
reign, they reviewed. Then at night
we're going to do, we're going to do a little
review of the previous lessons.
So we're going to start with the date. The
first word on the page has 1,
a dog.
And we're going to start with the second page. There's
a go-kart salesman
selling a car to a
couple. Just like you do.
And the way I like to review the
material from 8 years ago,
I like to do it with pictures because
pictures are easy to remember.
And lying in the middle, there was an image, and
beige. It's
supposed to be a good way to
remember
the new material too. Or sites, we
also have pictures, and then
everyone can check their own
understanding. Don't cover the words with your
hand
and look.  Look at the image
and try to remember what it
means. So tonight I'm going
to teach you the meaning of the
first six leafy images, and it's from
previous years' classes.
So starting tomorrow, we're going to
have a test. Something where I'm going to
choose a name from the list of
students
and I'm going to give them a microphone. I'll be there,
and they'll have their
chance to embarrass the
guy in front of 500 other people. Do
you understand?
So tomorrow I'm going to need a
way to be able to choose names.
It's the same.
[Music]
If you don't want to be on that list of
names, there will be
some money to get you removed. Okay,
we split the money. It's a good deal.
So the number of the first
image
is 109. We already did 108 previous ones.
We started this review last year.
So if you want the first 108, we
can give you the file digitally.
That's correct. Okay, that's
correct. We can find them on the
Nole Space page,
and it's free. It's free. Okay, okay.
So we're going to start with 109.
The image is a name selling a
car to a couple,
and in English we call them
used car salesmen.  It's almost a dirty word
in the US, as well as car purchases. The
last owner was an 80-year-old person.
She only used the car once a year
before it was to go to church. Come on,
this car is almost new,
so they would talk too much to
sell the car and it would break down the
following week. We
call them used car salesmen,
and their conversation, their pitch, is very
good. You would buy the car. In
English, we would say, "Good sales job."
And after talking with them, you would want to
buy the car. Software.
So why am I putting the image here?
And then in this tradition of hunger,
although it is suitable for
steps on the path, okay, it is a thousand
years old without tubes affected
in chin
when
256 in a book. So we are
rescuing this from various countries and
we made a catalog. We already have
300,
twenty thousand books.
We found her daughter, she of infinite. We already
found 320,000 books from
Mongolia, Russia,
Nepal, India, and we found those books. We
are transcribing. I think it will
take us five generations just to
type them. Have
the books contained in a single book. It is
called Hunger.
That is what you are studying. It
means number  One does this, number
two, number six, number three does this,
number four through six, you do
n't need to think too much, just follow
the steps 1 by 1 of the visitor class, and if
the class starts here on youtube.com,
skillful, and if you come every year, this next
year, okay, it was
always super cute
[Applause]
correctly say I went this year,
my friends from Singapore kidnapped me, we
went to Bali,
we had some VIP teachings, and then I said,
wow,
this is cuter than Thailand, so
Jasmine agreed, and next year we're going, okay,
here's what we agreed on
[Applause]
so here we have the [ __ ] idea of
bread
spell,
and here, here I am, here we are,
so this book
just does 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8,
we finish acting tumor, okay, you don't have to
think too much,
just come on, nobody to divide Thailand,
Thailand, Thailand, Bali, the leader, and
Bali Valley, Bali Valley, and Uruguay,
Hawaii
[Applause]
and then a J
Weiwei of future Hawaii is very close to
the truth than the tinder  Wenchuan, so
go one by one, you already have an abdomen,
then at the beginning of hunger,
Carstens, and selling used cars,
remember Windows? Now what I'm
doing now is resting, virus.
This is about these people.
This man is so good, you just have to
do 1, 2, 3, 4 and then get to the
Jewishness that you come, okay? That way it
's not traditional, interested in Buddhism,
Pickford and Ustari, and it says before
studying anything, anything
sweeter, or since the teacher has to
do a sales job,
coaching,
5 precious, precious,
if you have swing, you're going to be
able to see 500 years into the future, you're going to be
able to see that if you can
see every person in the world in 20
minutes
[Music]
and you can have love, direct love for
every person in the world, 7 billion
people in 20 minutes,
one by one in 20 minutes,
so that's called a sales job,
which indicates at the beginning of the wire,
Titus Soft, the audio master's job
is a Windows job, afternoon
girlfriend, you study Stella in the network,
you're going to be a Buddha  Few where I
am, so not only do I teach all
kinds of things, first tell people
what's cool, what's good, book
hungry, and then they're going to start
falling for this man, Peter, and over there,
and people are going to say, "Okay, now
teach me, because I'm telling you this
by admin, teaching hope of Finnish, because
my landing work is
half done, woman, I have six
more years of 18, and then your work, your
commitment to continue the
management of the next generation, I don't
have to do the dance tonight, it's already been
given to the next generation
who understand and have an attitude, so
you have to do the next thing,
okay? So before you teach all kinds of things,
tell people why it's so
good, why it's so good if they learn to
meditate,
if we do it, it's for this cause,
get a little closer, keep being,
she has trouble understanding me
because I talked to him,
no
[Music]
we do programs for
businessmen and we teach them to meditate,
they say, we don't want to
learn, education, innovation like in
Russia,
they say, we, I'm not Buddhist
I just want to do business
because I have to learn chin kachin
whatsapp everything invest because I have to
learn meditation
later if a businessman songs
Tuesday
learns to medicate good time good
medication of Cannes and textiles
they will be able to the new product of
next year this year have end of
those of them will be able to see the next
iPhone this year
Allende stock market if it's good
in the stock market reacts Nextel I'm going to see
which stock is going to go up
next year if you tell me a lot of
Sheriff's Deputy Joe so he has to
do it's a 20-day job
Gauntlet
Max businessman
you understand
and meditate every day
you'll see with the zones stocks that are going to go
up next year
I think I might be interested I'm
better than me so they have to sell
hunger
and meditation is a Buddhist tradition to
make students feel
attracted and from Beijing and now at the
beginning of this path
Wang there are people I had a person who
approached me and said when I
approach your programs many many
ideas much to think about
I just want to use my heart
I don't want to learn from the five steps
care
coaching I just  I want to be my
heart
in this tradition
[Music] You can't
open your heart without your
Stanford mind understanding. The pen comes first.
Without understanding the pen well, you can't
love. You can't open your
heart
because, like your husband, if your husband is
yelling at home, you denounce him, and then you
sit with Qatar, and after studying the
history of forgiveness, before you
take care of the pen in the record, you are angry
with the husband, and these opinions, if the
husband is yelling, after studying
the pen, who are you angry with,
my friend? Do you understand? You can't
call your husband 5. You can't
call another person if you don't
understand the seeds in this
tradition. You
can't love the husband, and where is it
in a mail? If you don't understand who
created it, okay? Do
you understand its industry? So, in
this tradition, with Whiting,
we think about opening the
heart. You can open your heart to your
husband if you understand that it is like the pen,
and if you think that the husband is a
person who gets angry, you will never have
a marriage. To do it, it is impossible.
You will have results in the word mails
33 min Sacramento starter fighting for
one.
You will have a truce
if you don't.  You understand who makes the husband,
you'll only have roses, it's impossible to
have a perfect marriage. I have a
perfect marriage,
the most beautiful thing in this world,
but it's not possible
in Filton's step. It's impossible if you don't
understand where the husband comes from.
Someone once came to me and said, "I need
your help. I've been
married to my husband for 30
years, and I'm from China.
In China, the woman has to cook; it's
destiny." I understand, and I don't complain about it.
I enjoy cooking for my family. I
can take on that responsibility.
But in 30 years of cooking for my husband, I've
never washed the dishes even once. So,
if there's any
way to change that with this
seed system,
then I taught him the four steps. I
want my husband to
find a meat partner.
I must help that person who has a
lot of work to do at home, a lot of
meditation, coffee. This
teaches the four steps, and the
following year he returned to his country. I
invite you to my house for dinner; I
have something to show you. And so I went
to his house,
and they have a very beautiful house. I'm not
going to tell you what city because you'll
guess who it belongs to.
So there's a big table and she
told me to sit down. It's time. No, there's
nothing on the table
except a little bell. So
I want to show you something.
She grabs the bell
and then the kitchen door opens and
her husband comes out and brings an
apron. Woman, Denise Light.
And then he's like this, he puts it on
and says, "Is the food nice?
No, no, not yet. I'm not doing Phillips now. Now I'm going to ask what I did
for the
kitchen."
And she looks at me.
What if I just
take two months?
[Music]
I did the four steps for two months and
started washing the dishes.
Then I started thinking about this because it
will stop here
and then you can also use the four
steps for the cook. And so I did it,
David Cook, and now he's cooking.
No Fighting, no fighting, 2 the sky, no
argument.
She didn't ask him to cook.
She didn't ask him to clean the
plants
because he
comes from her, so her husband has to
follow her seeds in tandem.
And that's it. So I can tell you,
just have a better one, go to your
house, have the best radios and  Tell
your husbands you love me, wine,
can you wash the dishes sometime?
And that's where the great
battle begins. Who understands? They are beings.
I insist, then, in the
seed system, the husband is like the pen. It
comes from 1,667, then it changes here.
Hastings 80, the husband keeps changing.
So tomorrow night there's
no feast. 9:15 after this
class, water expressed, I'm going to have a
special class. Five
thousand dollars to come, an invention.
Only men can come
out and tell how to plant the seeds
of a new waste of jeans so they never
have to wash the dishes.
[Applause]
Also, let's see who goes deeper.
Let's go deeper,
and this must be good. In the movie
Titanic
[Music],
this pickup was in the world. That
was the largest ship in the world in
Westwood, and it was new. Doctor First and
the news, and it was the first time it was
used in this too. So there
comes the Titanic First Sports, and there's
the iceberg mountain bike, a mountain of
landmarks and ice. If the ship hit
the iceberg,
big problem.  When they understand that
there is, this is why it's Percy and normal are
the seeds of the woman from Talca, not even
seen, male cid Englishman, the Titanic are
the seeds of the husband in his mind, it says
isport is husband hearts it's worth it is
are the 7th seed of the husband
washing the dishes and Titanic are the
seeds of
the woman cleaning the dishes,
who is going to win more but the seeds
of the woman the seeds of the husband which
seed is stronger
is impossible then nobody varied the
dishes that he is alive it can't be both
someone has to clean the dishes ok
and times erbol
hans werner sinn networking text
is impossible the husband has seeds
to wash it
the woman someone has to clean the
dishes probably invite you have to
wash the dishes
ok
the woman has to be stronger or the
seed of the man which is stronger than
you understand I'm going to
pour vodka picchu both
can be true in the husband's kitchen
the woman is washing the dishes
while in the woman's kitchen
the husband is the one who washes the cans I
leave you with big tub kitchen without a
cliché but how can  There are two kitchens
in one kitchen
before you, do you understand that the ok understand
also can be a pen or it can be
a good toy
[Music]
then we finish the first one and
then it's in this system river side
the true love of the extended has
understanding ok I
love my husband and I work on my seeds
and better than my husband and the husband
also improves the harmony in the kitchen you ca
n't have love without coaching ok
you have to think now directly
those indexes peace then in this step
20 path sorry I give state link
[Music]
learning is the path is the first step
you have to learn the instructions
that is the tradition ok if you learn about
the pen in the class
then then you use it at home
this is Buddhism ok this is our
tradition but first you learn from 'news
and then you use it
ok to cookies my soul's jockey this is
my sales job
and more at my house my partner but she
never next to the plants that although
they live
how do they think I cut my hand with a
kitchen knife no too
and I invited her to my class
too do you understand
[Music]
little sheath light
Light
and
I'm fine, I have,
then in the world there are many things
to know, like you, where, duck, like for
example, you learn from the pen, I'm going to
need the pen, you have
an extra pen,
she wants me to advertise her pen here, she
said, I said you,
before you come to my classes,
and don't think much about it for me.
[Music]
Next question from the spring of the
pen.
[Music] I do
n't care, help, just
use it, I do
n't care, will the pen come from
the pen, pen, come to me,
then then teach her, if you find out
where the water pen comes from,
then your
partner is going to wash the dishes
forever,
teach me the pen, teach me to relate
the pen from before,
this is a kind of darkness,
where does this pen come from, drachmas, it's
like darkness,
and then someone,
and a new light appears in your mind, it's
full of darkness, it's in the world
there are millions of things that one doesn't know, what
is good, but now one of them, big
game online, has just been illuminated,
then Buddhism
in the mix of light, to illuminate or to light up, to
clarify,
at the beginning of today, they highlight, it is for
you, this  It's the darkness,
nobody taught you about this at
your parents' school, they didn't talk about it, then you
come here, tag, to explain that
darkness, suddenly it clears up, so
if you come to Thailand, Thailand, Hannibal
and Bali, Balliva level and Hawaii
are there, so every time you come there's no
new light,
life in the market, new lights in the
mind, that's what we're doing,
this that indicated, is pitcher, this is the
meaning of the image, they can't hear
well,
the next image,
attacks
for 100 dollars,
blood,
someone, let's see, no professor, no
teacher can teach this image, it's
called to get
by fear,
wow, they
seek to explain, my daughter of times
and more,
and you have a microphone
[Music]
and you give me 200 dollars, if you're
wrong
I can do a little business,
on purpose, I'm looking for two things, the
answer has two main parts,
50 dollars and 50 dollars, okay, okay
[Music]
I'm going to repeat the question,
description, this image is called from the
last
wow
portal, in English it taught me that Ankara
[Music]
portable box,
mom is for evil, for example, it's
transportable, it
's  Portable, a self-test isn't portable, it's
too heavy to carry around.
[Music]
In it
So
Satan, if the answer is very long, most
likely he took each
[Music]
It's putting money in someone else's till, it
's a good answer, but not
for this question. There's someone else like that,
then they choose us, the cute one in the back, okay.
[Music]
And two parts to the question.
First part,
reality comes, moment of torment for
us.
The second part is the four steps. I mean, I
could be a
chalk teacher, and with that answer
to this attack
[Music]
Okay,
two parts,
yes,
a collection of merit and wisdom.
No, no,
we think that this ultimate reality
is found in anything that exists. That's
the first answer, and
my wife's second is you can share this
wisdom with anyone.
So it's the
last one, it's
the ultimate fortune to be able to
share with anyone, okay, okay,
that's the beginning of the answer.
[Music]
Well,
tell a joke.
I went to a very good restaurant with my
friends in Shenzhen. It
tends to be good, more tacky, more unequal.
So there's a bathroom on one side and another on the
other side,
Pixar, and there's a  Big sign,
good station, says the men's harm to
the left in the women's bathroom courtyard
to the direction of Saint. Below
the sign
in particular, it says men have to go
left because women is right
because women
are always right
and that's why your woman has a good
standard answer and not one of the number one things
is what you learn in this class that you wo
n't always have it here, you'll take it with you to
all ages. Watch more. If there's a
war tomorrow,
you lose your house
and you can't go back to your artist's house
and you have to stay in Dalian for the
rest of your days. Then you've lost
everything:
your car, home, house, mind, your
bank account, my family. Why, you know
I'm in this club, but in the blog, what
you learn in speculation you won't be
able to lose,
nobody can take it from you. There's a saying:
this is the only insured property you
can keep. On Facebook, you
can't keep your things. You learn things you
can keep here that cause ugly
bank accounts can fail,
apply, but a country can fail. A
rally that got sick with everything, you can fail
and biased, you can lose your arm, it
says again.  He took it into account and ate it, but
this idea no one can take away from you and you will
always have it. Richter makes
sure that it stops teeth. Second part
of the answer and Steve Austin, you can't
take with you what you win. And such is the only thing
that can take you with you. You ca
n't take your body and you can't
take your family. You can't
even take your name,
but these ideas
will remain on your website. It is a
fortune, it is something precious like
diamonds, your body, and above all, because of
this text. If the
whole world is destroyed, you can't keep it. You can
keep it in Ayutthaya, and if you die,
try to take it with you too. It
is u  A good answer
[Applause]
and by the way if you have a rosary and
you want me to bless it
then the program you can put up here
any day can
be
[Music]
maybe
in 15 minutes and it's ready the next
way the next image
[Music]
in English John Constable Shakespeare
is a phrase that comes from a Shakespeare play
maybe from Germany
anyway a man that we say
wants to buy in the video I think he
wants to buy success
and this powerful being says I can get it for you
come to Huanta where I live but
I need half a kilo of your meat you have to
cut
half a kilo
and I could take some from here I have a
little extra he
says give me half a kilo
because this way he can achieve
success for the rest of his days in
supposition there is a
very nice story
Shaw's very nice
and I'm going to criticize him he was a man who
liked to eat people
and eat those he had and he lives in
a cave
and he comes out and kidnaps people who
eat them or not so people
in the end know them this is how he does
2000 years in India
and if people see him everyone runs away he
is a very powerful being
and then there is a prince whose heart
is very pure in a one glove and one day he
is gifted that they
come to see him at the palace he reaches the heart
and he is going to take other people
and there is an incredible prince with a
pure heart and he was studying something a little bit
of hunger
[Music]
in the palace you
are here
that rate so he grabs two or three
people and then the prince says
or he approaches without fear everyone
runs away but the
prince says
if you need to eat someone he arrives in
Miami he says in that kind of heart
innocent people people don't bother
that house he says yes because it doesn't look quite
rich quite tasty so he
takes him to his cave
and then he puts him on the floor and starts to
generate a fire and then
the prince starts to cry
[Music]
good translation you are
supposed to be a prince of this
country and this is supposed to
be a comparable person
and with this I'm going to cook you what are you
talking about
[Music]
and he is waiting crying because to me
Because you want to scare me, I'm not afraid, so
why are you crying?
Fight my family while you haven't taken me out
of my class from hunger, oh dear,
this I threw myself into, decision, I didn't
have time to make the offering to the
teacher, he declared, and he has taken me out of the
class, it was exhausting, and now I'm going to die.
I had the chance, the opportunity to
thank my teacher, I want to
thank my teacher,
the prince, 17, a
press idea, the prince says kill the
monster
or punctured
in favor, let me go for half an hour and I
want to return to the palace,
Maite, I want to thank my teacher and not
make him an offering, and still not even Fort
Lawrence, they only teach me four
lines or a poem of New Game, and then he
returned to one to Copa, who blames himself
if I only want to go and thank
the mountain, he says, do you think I'm
our stupid one?
And then the prince imposes himself, if I don't
know who you think you are, so I have
honor, respect, the weapon, and that made
you, I don't know how it had to be, I'm going to
keep my word, I in principle,
you're killing for people, team, you're
eating people like you, I'm going to
keep my word, I have
yesterday, where did your  Father,
and well, when Juarez told him that, it was
a horseback ride because hunting
[Music]
things
what's the difference,
Juppé, your prince, your father, you eat
meat too, like you're just like me.
The prince gets like, software, no,
you're worse because, team, because you
eat people,
that's worse.
The monster tells him, because I'll be curious
and look to see if it's true that you're going to come back,
old man, because I think you're not going to come back.
I'm going to make the fire bigger and don't
see your master, sacrifice, say goodbye to your
master, and I'm going to wait for you to see if it's
true. I'm curious. And then the
prince,
hip hop, winehouse, in gold corporation
line,
then he paid him a thousand gold coins for
another line,
five,
and each line gave him ten thousand
pieces of gold.
Master, I'm going to have to go, I'm not going
back. I love you, I love you, I
hope that in the next life of my
parents we find each other. And then his father
asking him, more, is there to buy, Maeztu? I
promised to return, barbecue city, to the
asado. You do
n't have to keep this promise to
this person, a
king. You're not a good politician,
the king.  You have to be smart and not
the king has to make a promise but
if the promise isn't good the king has to
change it
[Music]
how are you going to run a country if you're so
honest the prince tells her
a good king keeps his word
[Music]
and 22 up to 1 a king keeps his
word so I'm leaving and back again
the amount was like I'm piqued has returned
there promised here eight months I promised
and I I keep my promises Stein you
're quite weird the prince tells her
I'm ready cook you killed me crab and
the monster gets angry Mayan theses this is
my house
I decide when I eat Abbott is something
I'm going to decide when I'm
going to cook you Watergate
Juve your cup what it
taught what they teach you well it
taught me a famous verse that U2
can you teach me
the meaning of the verse even if you
have to call JR even
if you have to cut the meat of one
time flies force for waits even if you have to
pay with a quarter with half a kilo
of your meat for a verse
in monsters is  Valuable,
then the master tells him,
and then he has like a garment around
his torso and puts him on the stone,
makes the contractions at first
[Music]
Teach me, you're a good one. So he
starts learning about weapons,
and then he saw the emptiness directly,
right, and what he likes is the story
[Applause]
And then he wants to say that it's a
valuable thing, that the weapon is something valuable, and it
comes to town.
If you have a lot of money for the
plane ticket to Hawaii,
don't doubt it's worth it, don't doubt that he
cuts his own flesh for this.
Working 17 years walking
to get these teachings, and now
you have 17 hours of flight,
3 hours in the plane, the
fort is up to 14 hours in customs,
and an hour to get here. It's
not so bad, you guys, but I lost
three hours,
okay, because with one number one
[Music]
This state,
this is talking about the relationship between
the student and his teacher,
how the relationship between them should be
internally. Very much in
Christie's tradition that there is
a false respect, like a
student doing and doing
three times like this
[Music]
We're all over the world.
I've served my teacher for 30 years. I
'm her cook, her
silver cleaner, and her laundryman.
And then I saw hundreds and hundreds of Swann's students.
This student in the show, respect,
nervous. Everyone. This type of
student
in my teacher's
back, back, they don't touch the chair. What do
you think you're doing? I
liked that. Many, many students like that stand out.
And then I saw the other type, the lama
camping. The lama comes in
and is like, do you think it's because I don't like it? It makes him
a nice tea.
Thank you for teaching me. And well, it turned out so
fun. And today, classes. Your class is so
fun. It makes me happy. It doesn't make me happy.
I calm it down. And it's Facebook
in this old space
because it looks like a dog.
And then the student also gets
attached. This is different from respect. It's
different from respect, but respect is
a little artificial.
Drama,
dena flexion, it affects it. I
love you. I have so much joy, so much
fun.
My husband is so much better. And I feel
like my Facebook. I
feel you like my favorite dog. It's that you're
the different feeling. Okay, it applies to
you. And surely, you're supposed to
think that between the teacher being
The Buddha and that you can get to
Thailand,
you have to respect him like the Buddha,
but there are two ways to respect
aspects, one is verbal respect
and they make you nervous, everyone
respects where you are,
you are my personal assistant
for 25 years,
and we have respect and honesty and
real respect, that goes typical private
tea party,
I start drinking the chocolate
and I already love you, we
need you to live a long time,
but you can't be attentive to many,
many six masters have to
respect me
[Music]
and I want you to stay here, this
way it feels different, apec
is affection,
which is a type of love and it's better than
respect, it's a higher warmth,
suddenly she treats herself like a pet
before coming up here, she
tries to show herself as a side,
those are true students of the
fun hunger, that's how the difference is always understood,
so in our lineage I am your
daughter
but they are a line, I think there are 43
and you, you have to remember
everyone
[Music]
more than two days,
Bojan and moving without serious names, it's going to
be in cell and better,
then we have respective the next and
You are the next masters
then certain and our lineage
is not very cold they are
like that and have fun
insight inside
inside very strict like here for so
much
everyone to dance
the mind is like that is strip wit of
behavior
like
before they understand you decision
this is your family you know
now we are you know
in this family the tradition for a thousand
years
is friendly is happy are fun
[Music]
giving more strict play correct
cited inputs 2,000 books
butterfield but he
the feeling is like a dog that
they understand 16 p this respect steak respect respect
true reflection
true respect is affection
they understand
is the same reason we leave one
more image and then we do questions and
answers
this is the last half hour and if
we are relaxed
ok
the questions and answers in Miami how
to finish Walmart but my job is to
finish one more medical image
three passages and Roberts for 100 dollars
Benitez has taught several times
raises his hand first
hitcher nothing that is a master or a
professor
I stay here I
wasn't relieving first there must be
more command believe him clearly  Inbursa
in Buddhism Woods I had a good student without a
lectern light from Twitter shouldn't be
like 3
although more capable to go out
ok first is first you can't teach
several teachings that's the first one you
shouldn't teach the first
teachings number 2 you should be
open to teachings the cup has to
be face up
while and well
number three they don't have to have a couple
of fats I Huelva
[Music]
we suspect that let's
see
very well thank you shopping jumping
bye bye ok
[Applause]
read
later ok ok ok we
finished the sixth we had the vendor
and heart like we had the light
fixed by the web we had the fortune on
your street by death
we had even cut off the meat
we had the affection of a dog widget
styps
and we had the three cups of Steve
have to know tomorrow night
something I'm going to corroborate I'm going to choose
a name I say that I'll mark you and you're going to
have the microphone ok ok Westbound
Jansen what's the wrong answer
then if you need a
bathroom break or a tea break want
to go if you want  go secretly to
their room,
well, you can do the castings back,
question time in Winchester, and we
have like 20 and 20 more minutes,
okay?
[Music]
Hello, hello, thank you for coming to teach us. I
have a question to ask
regarding death. If
I see a person in front of me and I see
you having difficulty
breathing, the two things I can do
in my mind are, first,
to reassure the person
[Music]
and teach the person about
the process of dying. The second thing is
[Music] I
remind the person of the good that
person has done in their life.
Apart from these two things, what other
things can I do to help this
person in the difficult moment of
breathing?
[Music]
And perhaps later that person dies,
how do I help that person
[Music]
when the person doesn't have
any kind of training for a
higher rebirth?
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] I
asked the resource,
yes, yes, what a
good question. Oh,
Haiti, I have asked this question to
my own teacher, that's the meaning of
the need,
and this is in  The Camps lineage, and when you
become a master,
you can say, "I heard this from my
master, okay,
this is lineage." So, in my case,
my father, me, and my father was a
very big, heavyset man.
He liked to hunt, he
killed a lot of animals,
and what a benefit, and he killed many other
times, and he even had a fishing boat
for fun. Fishing [ __ ], he would take us out
to fish for big fish in the
ocean.
Well, when I was little, when I was 17, he
taught us how to clear the
land, and I also killed a deer,
and he taught us all this,
and he also taught us how to clean the
fish and clean the deer with a
special knife—you
start down here
and you cut like this, and then you open it up, and you don't
eat those things, you just have to
remove them. You see with the deer
[Music]
you're completely covered in
blood, you have to remove the stomach. I
told my father, "I can't do it." He got
very angry.
We grew up in a cowboy place;
this is a custom in our
province and our state.
Here, a
young man kills a deer and fishes. I
said, "But I can't do it." He got very angry,
and then  He got cancer.
I was with my doctor. My son, your
father needs a special operation,
and we're going to start here and
cut it like this. Drama. And
I was like, and we're going to remove a
part of his leg, and we're going to...
I didn't know about karma at that time. That's
strange because it's exactly the
same cut we used for the PP, for
the fish, and for the deer. That's
strange.
Well, then my father had cancer. I
was studying Buddhism in Haiti, and
then I asked my style teacher, "
My mom, my father is dying from a
set of injuries. The operation opened him up, what can you
look inside
with him in
the last few weeks?" She
said to my teacher, "This question: What
can I do to help my father?" It
's a
very good Christian custom.
Some Christians, when a person
is dying,
tell them to go outside. Then
the priest is left alone with Father
Eastwood Azken, and the priest asks a
young man, "And do you have something with a bad seed
that you create that you want to talk about?" A
Hindu from a well in Buddhism, and he
affirms this: if you make any mistake, if
you commit an error in...  His life, if you tell
someone
and help clean the mountain, there's a
lot of Hampshire, and if you say, "Sorry,
I'm sorry, I wouldn't do it again,"
and then it's sad, that almost
includes the center. So my teacher
taught me to be able to
relate to your mother. One thing is the
first, which is to try to get her to
tell you all the bad things that come out of
them. Then the second, as you
said, make her
remember the
good things that are.
And you always taught me to respect
other people,
the businessman,
also teach to work hard. So
thank you for that. He was very good with
children. There were
four of us siblings. I
told him to be patient with us, so I
said thank you. So these are the two
things: one, and tell them if they want to clean
something up. Sometimes you have to do it. It's a
trick to deceive, although my father wasn't
religious.
He and the church, if my mother
put the noose around his neck, it wasn't
religion. He didn't like it much.
So I was thinking, I have to get him to confess. What can I do?
Then he's dying. He can't even
eat. I mean, he's gotten
very, very thin.
So I sat down  I watched TV with him
and said, "Dad, I
remember once you said you'd been
in the war. You told me you'd
killed a lot of people. You'd kill a
lot of people. Would you
do something like that again? Not too
bad, Tiff." And then I tricked him into confessing. There are
two of them, and that
way he cleansed those seeds by
agreeing. So you talk
to him like that, so they can do that. You do
n't have to tell him it's something
religious. If they talk about their bad
seeds or bad actions, one of
them says they wouldn't do it
again. That seed is almost gone.
So the last piece of advice
presented earlier: if a person dies
for four or nine
days, it's possible they're in the Bardo. What's it like
being in the Bardo for them?
Usually, they don't forget they're
dead,
so they appear alive. And
I'd say, "Why are you torturing me and nobody
can hear you?"
Then why are so many of
you my family?
Why are you beating me up? I
'm asking you questions live and
people are ignoring you. It was later. Now it
's the first hour or something. They get
very nervous
and then
dead.
It's possible that  There are up to 49 days left and they don't
want to be home,
so it's very likely that I hear
the voices he's saying. So it's very
good to talk about the good things my
father did.
Mike Pitcher cost part-time. I saw this.
My teacher said that the bard, the time
of the bard, is like the time of the
lottery.
Very conscious. In the wheel of life,
we go on the wheel of life,
slim, number 8, 9, 10. At this moment
you choose the seed of the next life. It's
very difficult,
Jackson de Paz. So I
asked my teacher
what the meaning is.
This is the benefit of being close to
your hand. I'll tell you the
next day at night. He also had
a bell. He
rings the bell upstairs.
He is the abbot and has the only
television in the monastery. It was supposed to be
for events,
but he calls me. He
likes to watch the news. So when
he heard the bell, he
had to go quite high up to his
rooms because there was something
important happening in his room. But
then he heard the bell and went
upstairs.
This is the answer to your question. I
already asked Trump. I ask you
without this special word.  In the gym and the
meditation of death,
here it is on television,
so every night in the US, at the
same time, 7 pm, there was
a special program, very nice, it was
very short,
when she came on television
and there was
a wheel and she wouldn't stop, she wouldn't stop, she would
put her hand in, she would choose a
lottery number
for the whole country,
like 20 million people waiting,
blues and pigments, will she have chosen my
name? And my teacher said, said that's
Twitter during death,
that person is like choosing the
lottery number.
In this life you have done very good things,
very bad things,
if you have millions, thousands, tenths of a
dollar, but one of them is what will determine
the next life.
So it is a very, very important moment to
say, is that seed going to save 70, 80
years,
you are going to be an animal, you become a human being,
a big nose, an active American analysis.
So this is the important moment,
so it is very important that before you talk to them about
the good things they
did, never, ever
with a person who is
dying, your dad, who is leaving behind a
gender, never, ever get angry  For me, with
people in that situation, everything calms down,
everything is very calm. Talk to them about
the good things they
said in their lives.
After they die, they are
listening to you, they are seeing it. It's your turn now,
so talk to your family.
You remember Dad,
the good things he did, and how he helped everyone
in 2015. He helped those
humble families and gave them good money.
We have a good father, but he is like this.
And if I won the lottery, I would be there at
that moment, and
you would help him have a good
rebirth. So it's very important during
the first seven weeks, 49 days.
The number on the day of death is
number one, and it's ahead. If they die at
11:59, it's still day one.
So for seven weeks, be
very careful in the
family home. Only talk about the good things you've
done because that person will be
listening. Where it's possible that just...
well, the last thing... and then
we'll go to sleep. Okay,
Jigme,
the name is
already showing. Twenty years ago,
his daughter died, and his daughter was only
20 years old. This is Jon, and she died very young. So I
came in. So
she came to me. She had her life
totally destroyed.
When parents die, it's very hard, and
if a son or daughter dies before, I think there's nothing like that.
This was completely... Christ
teaches us all this.
For seven weeks, speak well of your
daughter,
all the good things I've seen. I recently
told her that was 20 years ago. I think
better than here. I still
talk to my daughter every
night during coffee meditation,
and this is so beautiful. Shakespeare and
football... and we have such a good relationship, and
I'm very happy. I feel very fortunate,
Aitor, and I'm still one talking.  with her,
so there's no reason to stop after
seven weeks. You
can keep doing it for the rest of
your lives, and then you'll see them, you'll
meet them again.
That's the reason, the reason why
you become a Buddha. You'll
see them again, be together again.
So death is temporary, this
separation is permanent. And one reason
to study coaching
is to meet them again, and they'll be
in the same
Buddha paradise, and they'll be super
happy.
So don't worry, okay? And talk to
them,
and never fight with your relatives.
Have that moment, just talk about good things,
okay?
[Music]
So, sir,
to maintain the fan page,
the leader Beijing will guide the mandala
band. Okay, yes,
no?
[Music]
Yes,
and
5.
[Music]
Calm down, if the passion is
the brand.
[Music]
What was I going to say?
I
[Music]
are real,
that's a lot.
[Music]
And yes,
and I.
[Music]
Tampa, Fifth, and I